<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Bing: e-settlements</title>
    <link>http://www.bing.com:80/search?q=e-settlements</link>
    <description>Search results</description>
    <image>
      <url>http://www.bing.com:80/s/a/rsslogo.gif</url>
      <title>e-settlements</title>
      <link>http://www.bing.com:80/search?q=e-settlements</link>
    </image>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2020 Microsoft. All rights reserved. These XML results may not be used, reproduced or transmitted in any manner or for any purpose other than rendering Bing results within an RSS aggregator for your personal, non-commercial use. Any other use of these results requires express written permission from Microsoft Corporation. By accessing this web page or using these results in any manner whatsoever, you agree to be bound by the foregoing restrictions.</copyright>
    <item>
      <title>iSettlements</title>
      <link>https://www.isettlements.com.au/</link>
      <description>Delivering a friendly, reliable and personalised service, iSettlements is a boutique settlements agency assisting clients across a broad range of real estate transactions including: Strata …</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Nov 2020 14:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Services - BEST REAL ESTATE PROPERTY SETTLEMENT AGENT ...</title>
      <link>https://www.a1conveyancing.com.au/pexa-e-settlement/</link>
      <description>PEXA E-Settlement If you are looking to use the benefits of online PEXA e-settlement; A1 Conveyancing are an early adopter, winner Australia Wide Community Super User and PEXA registered, So we can assist with your title ‘e-settlement’ also referred to as ‘e-conveyancing’. To reap the benefits like Settle-me.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Nov 2020 05:10:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>E-conveyancing | InfoTrack</title>
      <link>https://www.infotrack.com.au/solutions/e-conveyancing/</link>
      <description>E-conveyancing - more than e-settlements. Did you know that all essential parts of the conveyancing process can now be done electronically including verification of identity, contracts, exchange, and settlement? If you are ready to adopt the end-to-end e-conveyancing process below, then you're in a great position to create more value for your firm, your clients and to stand out from your ...</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Nov 2020 00:51:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Property conveyancing and settlement | ANZ</title>
      <link>https://www.anz.com.au/personal/home-loans/tips-and-guides/conveyancing-and-settlement/</link>
      <description>On settlement day, conveyancers (or solicitors) and lenders get together to finalise finances and the transfer of the property. The balance of the purchase price is paid, plus or minus ‘adjustments’ for items such as council rates (to make sure buyer and seller have paid the appropriate amount each).</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Nov 2020 21:10:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trends in Payments, Clearing and Settlement Systems ...</title>
      <link>https://www.rba.gov.au/publications/annual-reports/psb/2017/trends-in-payments-clearing-and-settlement-systems.html</link>
      <description>Payments System Board Annual Report – 2017 Trends in Payments, Clearing and Settlement Systems . The Payments System Board monitors trends in retail payments, and activity and risk exposures across financial market infrastructure (high-value payment systems, securities settlement systems and central counterparties), consistent with its responsibilities to promote efficiency and competition ...</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Nov 2020 02:04:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Queensland, Settle on better | PEXA</title>
      <link>https://www.pexa.com.au/sites/qld</link>
      <description>PEXA Key is the new settlement app for buyers and sellers, available in Queensland and across Australia.. It has already helped 35,000 Australians through settlement, safeguarding more than $22.5 billion worth of property. PEXA Key has the ability to securely transfer important account information, while giving buyers and sellers a countdown to their settlement plus access to checklists and ...</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Nov 2020 18:32:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Settlement day | Your rights, crime and the law ...</title>
      <link>https://www.qld.gov.au/law/housing-and-neighbours/buying-and-selling-a-property/buying-a-home/tips-for-new-home-owners/settlement-day</link>
      <description>Settlement day is usually 4–6 weeks after the contract is finalised, but this can be whatever length of time you negotiate with the seller. Almost all settlements are completed within a range of 30–90 days after the contract is finalised. Council rates and other fees The seller must pay the rates up to (and including) the day of settlement.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Nov 2020 18:02:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Settlement - Wikipedia</title>
      <link>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Settlement</link>
      <description>Settlement may refer to: . Human settlement, a community where people live; Settlement (structural), the distortion or disruption of parts of a building Settlement (closing), the final step in executing a real estate transaction Settlement (finance), where securities are delivered against payment of money Settlement (litigation), a resolution between disputing parties about a legal case</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Nov 2020 21:04:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Home | PEXA</title>
      <link>https://www.pexa.com.au/</link>
      <description>Your e-Conveyancing Community If you’re a property industry professional, join the e-Conveyancing Community to post questions and find answers regarding property lodgements or financial settlements from industry peers and PEXA experts.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Nov 2020 16:29:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Human settlement - Wikipedia</title>
      <link>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Human_settlement</link>
      <description>In geography, statistics and archaeology, a settlement, locality or populated place is a community in which people live. The complexity of a settlement can range from a small number of dwellings grouped together to the largest of cities with surrounding urbanized areas.Settlements may include hamlets, villages, towns and cities.A settlement may have known historical properties such as the date ...</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Nov 2020 20:06:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Making e-Settlements Simple | Sympli</title>
      <link>https://www.sympli.com.au/</link>
      <description>An e-settlements service built by users, for users. We’ve spoken with thousands of lawyers and conveyancers from across the industry to identify what you want to see in an e-settlements service. The result is an efficient and user-friendly platform shaped by your feedback.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Nov 2020 08:13:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>e-Settlement Services | Sympli - Making e-Settlements Simple</title>
      <link>https://www.sympli.com.au/e-settlement-services/</link>
      <description>e-Settlement Services Designed by users, for users. You’ve told us what you need to conduct e-Settlements with confidence and our highly experienced team have taken your feedback to develop a service that’s efficient, easy to use, reliable and secure.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Nov 2020 21:45:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Settlement Agents Perth WA | Residential Settlements ...</title>
      <link>https://www.tenantsettlements.com.au/</link>
      <description>Settlement Agents Perth - Perth’s trusted team of settlement agents, Licensed Real Estate Settlement Agency specialising in residential settlements.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Nov 2020 16:58:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>E settlements - Settlement agents perth | conveyance ...</title>
      <link>https://www.tenantsettlements.com.au/e-settlements/</link>
      <description>E settlements. December 11, 2017 | In Uncategorized | By Settlement Agents Perth. A huge change is coming to the real estate industry and unfortunately it will be a cost to you. For each settlement you will be charged over a $100 more, plus your Bank will have further fees. This change is called “E settlements”, meaning all settlements will be done on line after the 1 st May 2018. Spread ...</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jul 2020 00:43:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Settlements Jobs in All Australia - SEEK</title>
      <link>https://www.seek.com.au/jobs-in-banking-financial-services/settlements</link>
      <description>Find your ideal job at SEEK with 40 jobs found for Banking &amp; Financial Services, Settlements in All Australia. View all our vacancies now with new jobs added daily!</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Nov 2020 14:38:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>e-settlements: mandates, challenges and opportunities ...</title>
      <link>https://www.lawyersweekly.com.au/podcast/25874-e-settlements-mandates-challenges-and-opportunities</link>
      <description>This special episode is brought to you by InfoTrack, and unpacks all things e-settlements for practitioners moving forward.. In this special episode of The Lawyers Weekly Show, brought to you by InfoTrack, Jerome Doraisamy and InfoTrack CEO John Ahern discuss some of the issues facing lawyers and conveyancers when it comes to navigating mandates for e-settlements, how to turn such hurdles into ...</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2020 13:52:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How will e-Settlements work when there are two providers ...</title>
      <link>https://www.infotrack.com.au/news-and-insights/how-will-e-settlements-work-when-there-are-two-providers/</link>
      <description>In an e-conveyancing context, interoperability is the ability for two or more ELNOs to communicate with one another via the sharing of an agreed data set, thereby allowing freedom of choice between which platform you use. There is currently an industry forum working through the possible solutions to competition and interoperability.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Nov 2020 13:31:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is Pexa safe to use for e-settlements? | Prime Property ...</title>
      <link>https://www.primepropertylawyers.com.au/is-pexa-safe/</link>
      <description>In a previous blog post, I explained how e-settlements work. Pexa has significant security safeguards in place to ensure that only authorised individuals and firms can use the system. They must have their identity verified in person by a Pexa agent, and are issued with a personalised digital key. From what I understand, the security breach began with the conveyancer’s email account. The ...</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Nov 2020 12:40:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MSA National - MSA goes live with e-Settlements via PEXA ...</title>
      <link>https://www.msanational.com.au/msa-esettlements-via-pexa-digiSettle.htm</link>
      <description>MSA goes live with e-Settlements via PEXA = DigiSettle MSA has gone live with PEXA settlements in VIC, NSW and WA. All service providers in the mortgage industry can now conduct PEXA settlements, but the way MSA does it through our DigiSettle technology is truly a work of digital art. It delivers an end-to-end solution that is unparalleled.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Oct 2020 22:20:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Viking Settlement | Forge of Empires Wiki | Fandom</title>
      <link>https://forgeofempires.fandom.com/wiki/Viking_Settlement</link>
      <description>The Viking Settlement is the first of the Cultural settlements. The purpose is to lead the Vikings to prosperity as the Thane of their new village. This page explains the workings of the settlement and it's buildings, for information about the quests, embassy advancements and rewards check the Vikings page. 1 Start 2 Embassy 3 Buildings 3.1 Building Menu 3.2 Residential Buildings 3.3 Cultural ...</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Nov 2020 05:16:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Future of eSettlements - triSearch</title>
      <link>https://www.trisearch.com.au/the-future-of-esettlements/</link>
      <description>If you want to hear more about “The Future of eSettlements”, Sympli CEO, David Wills, and triSearch CEO, Taylah Allen have an in-depth webinar on Tuesday 27 March where they will cover off on topics of the eSettlement industry, price, security and give a demonstration of the new Sympli platform.. Register for this complimentary webinar here and receive 1 CPD point.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Nov 2020 18:43:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PG&amp;E Settlement and Voting Information - PGELawsuitGuide</title>
      <link>https://www.pgelawsuitguide.com/pge-settlement/</link>
      <description>Saturday November 28, 2020 — PG&amp;E filed for voluntary Chapter 11 bankruptcy to restructure its finances and resolve the company’s extensive wildfire liabilities.. On December 6, 2019, attorneys representing fire survivors in the bankruptcy case reached a settlement with PG&amp;E, known as the Restructuring Support Agreement (or “RSA”).</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Nov 2020 09:58:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>South Australia legislates to boost property e-settlements</title>
      <link>https://onboarding.pexa.com.au/files/160706_SA_LegislatesToBoostPropertyEsettlements_BankingDay.pdf</link>
      <description>South Australia legislates to boost property e-settlements 06 July 2016 The potential market for the real property e-settlement system, PEXA, has been expanded with the passing of legislation allowing e-conveyancing in South Australia. Using a similar method to how the ASX transacts, PEXA acts as an online exchange for financial institutions, lawyers, conveyancers and state-based land ...</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Nov 2020 15:53:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MasterChef finalist caught in conveyancing hacker attack</title>
      <link>https://www.smh.com.au/business/companies/masterchef-finalist-caught-in-conveyancing-hacker-attack-20180622-p4zn4o.html</link>
      <description>A former MasterChef contestant and her family are homeless after hackers stole $250,000 from the proceeds of their home sale while it was being settled on Australia’s new online property ...</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Nov 2020 03:46:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How e-settlements divided an industry arguing over costs ...</title>
      <link>https://www.abc.net.au/news/2017-11-11/e-conveyancing-to-hit-wa-buyers-and-sellers/9139756</link>
      <description>The WA conveyancing industry is warring over whether to support a push to mandate electronic property settlements rather than the old paper-based system.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Feb 2019 13:26:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PeopleSoft eSettlements Overview - Oracle</title>
      <link>https://docs.oracle.com/cd/E39583_01/fscm92pbr0/eng/fscm/fmpy/concept_PeopleSofteSettlementsOverview-9f40e8.html</link>
      <description>Buyer Direct Model: In this implementation, a single buying organization (buyer) controls the application. This model is based on a one-to-many relationship: one buyer provides an interface for many suppliers.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Nov 2020 08:13:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PeopleSoft eSettlements Datasheet</title>
      <link>http://www.oracle.com/us/media/ebook/e-ds-esettlements-194909.pdf</link>
      <description>ORACLE DATA SHEET 2 defines appropriate rules and roles. Select, review, and approve payments automatically or manually. Route invoice line items for approval to different managers simultaneously, resulting in faster payment processing and the ability to take early payment discounts. This capability is especially useful for consolidated invoices from</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Nov 2020 22:52:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>E-Settlements - Tech</title>
      <link>https://it.toolbox.com/question/e-settlements-031507</link>
      <description>E-Settlements. I need some documentation for E-Settlements. I have never heard of this module and I need to put together some fast documentation. Does anybody have any doc's they could share with me? i.e. Scoping document, Questionnaire, Process Flows, configuration, testing scripts?? Thanks in advance! My Email is email@removed. share this c. czarr. c. czarr. 0 Follower 0 Following Follow ...</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Nov 2020 08:29:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A second e-settlements platform will end the PEXA ...</title>
      <link>https://www.legalpracticeintelligence.com.au/a-second-e-settlements-platform-will-end-pexas-monopoly/</link>
      <description>The combination of mandated e-settlements and a single operator had the makings of a monopoly marketplace. A second operator will instantly end any such monopoly. Legal Practice Intelligence has contacted InfoTrack for a response to the AFR article. Check back for further updates.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Nov 2020 03:47:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PeopleSoft eSettlements Overview - Oracle</title>
      <link>https://docs.oracle.com/cd/E39583_01/fscm92pbr0/eng/fscm/fmpy/concept_PeopleSofteSettlementsOverview-9f40f2.html</link>
      <description>PeopleSoft eSettlements, a global electronic invoice presentation and payment (EIPP) solution, enables you to optimize the settlement process with electronic invoices and payments, matching, online approval and dispute resolution, and email notifications.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Nov 2020 13:24:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PeopleSoft Enterprise eSettlements - Oracle</title>
      <link>https://www.oracle.com/a/ocom/docs/applications/peoplesoft/peoplesoft-esettlements.pdf</link>
      <description>Reduce the time and effort to receive, approve, and pay invoices by using best practice processes in PeopleSoft eSettlements. Buyer benefits include:</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Nov 2020 05:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PG&amp;E Fire Settlements (2019) | PG&amp;E Wildfire Settlement ...</title>
      <link>https://www.norcalfirelawyers.com/pge-fire-settlements/</link>
      <description>In June 2019, PG&amp;E reached a $522 million settlement for the Camp Fire, under which it would pay Paradise $270 million and pay $252 million to Butte County, according to the Wall Street Journal. The payouts on any Camp Fire settlements will not occur unless and until they are approved by the bankruptcy judge.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Nov 2020 03:58:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Western Australian Conveyancers Association to Oppose ...</title>
      <link>https://www.legalpracticeintelligence.com.au/western-australian-conveyancers-association-to-oppose-compulsory-e-settlements-2/</link>
      <description>Mandated e-settlements will accomplish industry adoption. According to a report in the AFR last week, Marcus Price, the CEO of PEXA stated that PEXA currently manages 20 per cent of all refinancing transactions and only up to 4 per cent of all transactions in the transfers market. The registrars’ decisions mean those percentages will soar, Mr ...</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2020 10:51:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Celebrating 100 e-Settlements on Melbourne Cup day</title>
      <link>https://www.tuckfields.com.au/celebrating-100-e-settlements-on-melbourne-cup-day/</link>
      <description>Celebrating 100 e-Settlements on Melbourne… Nov 6 2018. General Conveyancing. Celebrating 100 e-Settlements on Melbourne Cup day with PEXA. Many celebrated Melbourne Cup day on Tuesday 6th November 2018 however, Tuckfields had so much more to celebrate with the official announcement by PEXA of settling over 100 properties in the electronic space! CEO Tammy Edwards is proud of her team who ...</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Nov 2020 11:13:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Electronic Settlements (MSupplier) | U of M Procurement</title>
      <link>http://procurement.umich.edu/supplier-resources/supplier-portal/electronic-settlements</link>
      <description>Electronic Settlements enable suppliers that have been invited into the MSupplier Portal by the University of Michigan to: Submit electronic invoices - cXML or flat file</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Nov 2020 09:55:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US: All Settlement Products to be Labeled ‘Made in Israel ...</title>
      <link>https://www.jewishpress.com/news/us-news/us-all-settlement-products-to-be-labeled-made-in-israel/2020/11/19/</link>
      <description>Shiloh and Psagot wineries' products at the Knesset hosted event marking the launch of a new Israeli Wine Guide including wines from Judea and Samaria. During Secretary of State Mike Pompeo’s ...</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Nov 2020 17:25:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Divorce Settlement: What Is And Isn't Fair?</title>
      <link>https://divorcedmoms.com/divorce-settlement-what-is-and-isnt-fair/</link>
      <description>There can be a huge difference between an equitable divorce settlement and a fair divorce settlement. In the hope of helping those who are in the dark about what is and isn’t a fair divorce settlement, here is a collection of examples of different scenarios and what we believe to be fair divorce settlements.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Nov 2020 19:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Infotrack, ASX find property exchange Sympli irresistible</title>
      <link>https://www.smh.com.au/business/companies/infotrack-asx-find-property-exchange-sympli-irresistible-20180531-p4zir3.html</link>
      <description>Victoria proposes to make e-settlements mandatory in October this year, while NSW intends to follow suit in July next year. In the meantime many parties - small conveyancing firms in particular ...</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Nov 2020 14:29:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CT&amp;E Settlements - Overview, News &amp; Competitors | ZoomInfo.com</title>
      <link>https://www.zoominfo.com/c/ct-e-settlements-llc/395799289</link>
      <description>View CT&amp;E Settlements (www.ctesettlements.com) location in Virginia, United States , revenue, industry and description. Find related and similar companies as well as employees by title and much more.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Oct 2020 00:58:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CT&amp;E (About Us) - CT&amp;E Settlements</title>
      <link>http://ctesettlements.com/about</link>
      <description>At CT&amp;E Settlements, our commitment is excellence. Therefore, we offer the best services conducting settlements. Some things to expect at CT&amp;E Settlements: We offer a flexible schedule that suits our clients needs. We return phone calls promptly. Title examination will be done in 3-5 working days. If there are any delays, we will contact you immediately. Funds will be treated in a professional ...</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Nov 2020 00:22:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PG&amp;E announces $13.5-billion settlement for California ...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/california/story/2019-12-06/pge-settlement-fire-northern-california</link>
      <description>PG&amp;E is an investor-owned utility that, critics say, too often puts short-term profits before necessary safety measures. The Camp fire, which raced through Paradise in 2018, killed 86 people and ...</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Nov 2020 15:46:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PG&amp;E Campfire Lawsuit Attorney | Matthews and Associates ...</title>
      <link>https://pgefirelawsuits.com/</link>
      <description>PG&amp;E Bankruptcy doesn’t end claims (February 28, 2019) PG&amp;E Corporation’s bankruptcy filing last month doesn’t end Camp Fire claims, according to a plaintiff’s attorney working in Chico, California. “PG&amp;E declared bankruptcy to try to hide from the liability of killing or injuring people in the Camp Fire,” said attorney Peter de la Cerda who represents several Camp Fire victims who ...</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Nov 2020 02:17:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Were ever any Quilombos, i.e. settlements created by ...</title>
      <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/AskHistorians/comments/k1raja/were_ever_any_quilombos_ie_settlements_created_by/</link>
      <description>Hello r/AskHistorians!You may already know me on here as someone who answers the occasional question about George Orwell, or the author of numerous over-enthusiastic posts about the recent AskHistorians Digital Conference. During the day, however, I'm a historian of 1930s Europe - more particularly, of the ways in which people responded to the Spanish Civil War of 1936-9.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Nov 2020 01:38:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lt &amp; E Settlements, LLC in Temple Hills, MD | Company Info ...</title>
      <link>https://www.bizapedia.com/md/lt-e-settlements-llc.html</link>
      <description>Lt &amp; E Settlements, LLC is a Maryland Domestic LLC filed on February 23, 2001. The company's filing status is listed as Forfeited and its File Number is W06171292. The Registered Agent on file for this company is Valerie Langham and is located at 11944 Autumn Wood Lane, Fort Washington, MD 20744.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Oct 2020 06:40:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Final Major Settlement, PG&amp;E Reaches Agreement to ...</title>
      <link>https://www.pgecurrents.com/2019/12/06/in-final-major-settlement-pge-reaches-agreement-to-resolve-individual-claims-relating-to-the-2017-and-2018-wildfires-and-the-2015-butte-fire/</link>
      <description>PG&amp;E Has Now Reached Settlements with All Major Groups of Wildfire Claimants. PG&amp;E Achieves Fully-Funded Equity Backstop Commitments. Company on Path to Making Major Changes Necessary to Exit Bankruptcy Ahead of June 30, 2020, Deadline</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Nov 2020 12:04:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PG&amp;E Fire Victims Warn Market Turmoil Endangers Their ...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2020-03-25/pg-e-fire-victims-warn-market-turmoil-endangers-their-settlement</link>
      <description>Victims of wildfires blamed on PG&amp;E’s equipment are concerned the sell-off on Wall Street could hobble stock payments that make up half of a $13.5 billion settlement over claims from the blazes ...</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Nov 2020 13:30:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PG&amp;E reaches $11 billion settlement relating to wildfire ...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/09/13/pge-reaches-11-billion-settlement-relating-to-wildfire-claims.html</link>
      <description>PG&amp;E said it has reached an $11 billion settlement agreement with entities representing about 85% of insurance subrogation claims relating to 2017 and 2018 wildfires.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Nov 2020 00:16:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PG&amp;E pleads guilty to involuntary manslaughter in Camp ...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/california/story/2020-03-23/pge-pleads-guilty-to-84-counts-of-manslaughter-over-paradise-fire</link>
      <description>PG&amp;E said it reached a settlement with the Butte County district attorney’s office on March 17. The utility's critics say the plea deal is too lenient.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Nov 2020 03:30:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Digital Energy Market ENTSO-E Settlements ENTSO-E</title>
      <link>https://www.ge.com/digital/asset/settlements-entso-e-ge-digital</link>
      <description>Market ENTSO-E Settlements ENTSO-E gedigitalenergy.com. To maintain our high levels of customer service, GE is committed to following the evolution of the ENTSO-E and CIM standards with the continuous development of our product solutions and to implement all major ENTSO-E standard evolutions within the Market and Settlement products. GE experts are providing an active contribution to the ...</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Nov 2020 19:40:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>